<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sploosh Kaboom</string>

    <!-- Menu Text -->
    <string name="menu_text_intro">Velcome to zee fleet! I am zee great Adminral WHISKY! Look Sharp, for vee are zee sole protectors of zis island</string>
    <string name="menu_text_start_1">Admiral! Red alert! All hands on deck!</string>
    <string name="menu_text_start_2">Sonar shows that schools of deadly giant squid are approaching! All ships prepare for battle!</string>
    <string name="menu_text_start_3">There are three squid groups: a large one, a medium one, und a small one! If vee allow zem to come any closer, zee children on zee island vill be in grave danger!</string>
    <string name="menu_text_start_4">Sailor! Take command of our new radar system to seek out and sink all of zese fiendishly hidden enemies!</string>
    <string name="menu_text_start_5">But be varned… you haff only 24 cannonballs zat you can fire.</string>
    <string name="menu_text_start_6">To destroy zee marauding squid pods, you must score four direct hits on zee large, three on zee medium, und two on ze small!</string>

    <!-- Shop Text -->
    <string name="shop_text_intro_1">OHHHHH! A customer! Welcome to Beedle\'s Shop! I deal in pretty much anything and everything!</string>
    <string name="shop_text_intro_2">Do you see anything you\'d like to buy? Just use your finger to browse.</string>
    <string name="shop_text_idle">Oh, just use your finger to browse.</string>
    <string name="shop_text_browse_item_1">Heart Container [rupees_1] Rupees\nThis is a very rare piece of heart! Obtaining it will surround you with a lot of love!</string>
    <string name="shop_text_browse_item_2">Treasure Map [rupees_2] Rupees\nA map to a hidden treasure! Oh, I found this playing Sploosh/Kaboom myself!</string>
    <string name="shop_text_browse_item_3">Triforce [rupees_3] Rupees\nThis is an object from the Goddesses! It is said to have mysterious powers reaching through time!</string>
    <string name="shop_text_buy_item_1">You got a Heart Container!\nYou can look up your obtained items in the Inventory section</string>
    <string name="shop_text_buy_item_2">You got a Treasure Map!\nYou can look up your obtained items in the Inventory section</string>
    <string name="shop_text_buy_item_3">You got a Triforce!\nYou can look up your obtained items in the Inventory section</string>
    <string name="shop_text_bye">Bye! Come again!</string>

    <!-- Inventory Text -->
    <string name="inventory_text_heart_piece">A voucher for a massage with happy ending!\n😙 mau mau 😙</string>
    <string name="inventory_text_triforce">Behind every picture rests a deeper meaning, especially taken ages ago!</string>

    <!-- Win Text -->
    <string name="win_text">Congratulations! You won [rupees] Rupees!</string>

</resources>